<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Portfolios &#8211; Impact</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/all/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1</link>
	<description>Your Path Way To Independance</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:45:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Photoshop</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/photoshop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Image Editing Basics: You&#8217;ll learn essential image editing techniques, such as cropping, resizing, and adjusting brightness, contrast, and colors. The workshop may cover topics like working with layers, selection tools, and using different brush types.</li>



<li>Retouching and Restoration: Photoshop is widely used for retouching and restoring images. The workshop may delve into techniques for removing blemishes, wrinkles, or unwanted elements from photos. It may also cover restoring old or damaged photos.</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="952" height="867" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/portfolio-3-img-2.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-31"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Programming</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/programming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Hands-on Exercises: Workshops typically include hands-on exercises to practice coding. You&#8217;ll be given coding challenges or projects to work on under the guidance of the instructor. These exercises help reinforce the concepts you learn and provide an opportunity to apply them in practical scenarios.</li>



<li>Problem Solving and Algorithms: Programming is not just about syntax; it&#8217;s also about problem-solving. The workshop may cover algorithmic thinking, problem-solving strategies, and how to break down complex problems into smaller, manageable steps.</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-style-default"><img decoding="async" width="1366" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Screenshot-14.png" alt="" class="wp-image-210"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Video Editor</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/video-editor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Introduction to Video Editing: The workshop will likely start with an overview of video editing fundamentals. This may include understanding various video formats, resolution, frame rates, and aspect ratios.</li>



<li>Introduction to Editing Software: You&#8217;ll learn about popular video editing software such as Adobe Premiere Pro, Final Cut Pro, or DaVinci Resolve. The workshop may focus on one specific software or provide an overview of multiple options.</li>



<li>Basic Editing Techniques: You&#8217;ll learn essential editing techniques such as importing media, organizing files, timeline navigation, trimming clips, and adding transitions.</li>



<li>Advanced Editing Techniques: The workshop will cover more advanced editing techniques, such as working with multiple video and audio tracks, using effects and filters, color correction, and audio editing.</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="952" height="867" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/portfolio-2-img-1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-32"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pottery</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/pottery/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Define the Workshop Objective: Determine the specific focus of your pottery workshop. Are you teaching hand-building techniques like pinch, coil, and slab construction, or will you be focusing on wheel throwing? Clarify your objective to guide the workshop preparation.</li>



<li>Plan the Workshop Duration: Decide on the duration of your workshop. Consider the complexity of the techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching and the time required for participants to practice and create their pottery pieces. It could be a one-day workshop or spread over multiple sessions.</li>



<li>Secure a Venue: Find a suitable venue for your pottery workshop. Look for a space that has enough room for participants to work comfortably and for you to set up the necessary equipment and supplies. Ensure the venue has access to utilities like water and electricity, depending on the pottery techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching.</li>
</ol>



<div class="wp-block-group is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.25.35-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-203"/></figure>
</div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Printing</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/printing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Define the Workshop Objective: Determine the specific focus of your workshop. Are you teaching a particular printing technique, such as screen printing or block printing? Or are you covering a broader range of printing methods? Clarify your objective to guide the workshop preparation. Plan the Workshop Duration: Decide on the duration of your workshop. Consider [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><br>Define the Workshop Objective: Determine the specific focus of your workshop. Are you teaching a particular printing technique, such as screen printing or block printing? Or are you covering a broader range of printing methods? Clarify your objective to guide the workshop preparation.</p>



<p>Plan the Workshop Duration: Decide on the duration of your workshop. Consider the complexity of the techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching and the time required for participants to practice and create their prints. It could be a one-day workshop or spread over multiple sessions.</p>



<p>Secure a Venue: Find a suitable venue for your workshop. Look for a space that has enough room for participants to work comfortably and for you to set up the necessary equipment and supplies. Ensure the venue has access to utilities like water and electricity, depending on the printing techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching.</p>



<p>Gather Equipment and Supplies: Determine the specific printing techniques you&#8217;ll be covering and gather the necessary equipment and supplies accordingly. This might include printing screens, squeegees, ink, printing blocks, carving tools, printing presses (if applicable), paper, fabric, and any other materials needed for the chosen techniques.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="768" height="1024" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.26.01-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-198"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leather</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/leather/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 20:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Leather bags and purses: Craftsmen can create a wide range of bags, from small clutches to larger tote bags, using different leather types and techniques.</li>



<li>Wallets and cardholders: These are often designed to be compact and practical, with slots for cards, cash, and other essentials.</li>



<li>Belts: Leather belts are typically handmade and can be customized with various buckles, colors, and textures.</li>



<li>Shoes and boots: Artisans skilled in shoemaking can produce high-quality leather footwear, ranging from casual shoes to formal dress shoes or sturdy boots.</li>



<li>Accessories: Leather can be transformed into accessories like bracelets, cuffs, keychains, and watch straps.</li>



<li>Leather garments: Some craftsmen specialize in creating leather jackets, vests, pants, or skirts.</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.25.58-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-190"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Resin</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/resin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Determine the Workshop Focus: Decide on the specific type of resin workshop you want to offer. It could be an introductory workshop for beginners, a workshop focused on a particular resin technique (e.g., resin pouring, resin casting, resin jewelry making), or an advanced workshop for experienced resin artists.</li>



<li>Plan the Workshop Content: Develop a curriculum or outline that covers the key concepts, techniques, and skills participants will learn during the workshop. Break it down into smaller modules, and consider providing step-by-step instructions, demonstrations, and examples.</li>



<li>Gather Materials and Tools: Identify the necessary materials and tools for the workshop, depending on the specific projects or techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching. This may include epoxy resin, silicone molds, mixing cups and sticks, pigments or dyes, protective gloves and aprons, heat guns or torches for removing bubbles, and a well-ventilated workspace</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.27.26-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-183"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
