<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>handmade &#8211; Impact</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio-cat/handmade/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1</link>
	<description>Your Path Way To Independance</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:16:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Pottery</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/pottery/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Define the Workshop Objective: Determine the specific focus of your pottery workshop. Are you teaching hand-building techniques like pinch, coil, and slab construction, or will you be focusing on wheel throwing? Clarify your objective to guide the workshop preparation.</li>



<li>Plan the Workshop Duration: Decide on the duration of your workshop. Consider the complexity of the techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching and the time required for participants to practice and create their pottery pieces. It could be a one-day workshop or spread over multiple sessions.</li>



<li>Secure a Venue: Find a suitable venue for your pottery workshop. Look for a space that has enough room for participants to work comfortably and for you to set up the necessary equipment and supplies. Ensure the venue has access to utilities like water and electricity, depending on the pottery techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching.</li>
</ol>



<div class="wp-block-group is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.25.35-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-203"/></figure>
</div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Printing</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/printing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 21:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=197</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Define the Workshop Objective: Determine the specific focus of your workshop. Are you teaching a particular printing technique, such as screen printing or block printing? Or are you covering a broader range of printing methods? Clarify your objective to guide the workshop preparation. Plan the Workshop Duration: Decide on the duration of your workshop. Consider [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><br>Define the Workshop Objective: Determine the specific focus of your workshop. Are you teaching a particular printing technique, such as screen printing or block printing? Or are you covering a broader range of printing methods? Clarify your objective to guide the workshop preparation.</p>



<p>Plan the Workshop Duration: Decide on the duration of your workshop. Consider the complexity of the techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching and the time required for participants to practice and create their prints. It could be a one-day workshop or spread over multiple sessions.</p>



<p>Secure a Venue: Find a suitable venue for your workshop. Look for a space that has enough room for participants to work comfortably and for you to set up the necessary equipment and supplies. Ensure the venue has access to utilities like water and electricity, depending on the printing techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching.</p>



<p>Gather Equipment and Supplies: Determine the specific printing techniques you&#8217;ll be covering and gather the necessary equipment and supplies accordingly. This might include printing screens, squeegees, ink, printing blocks, carving tools, printing presses (if applicable), paper, fabric, and any other materials needed for the chosen techniques.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="768" height="1024" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.26.01-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-198"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leather</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/leather/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 20:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Leather bags and purses: Craftsmen can create a wide range of bags, from small clutches to larger tote bags, using different leather types and techniques.</li>



<li>Wallets and cardholders: These are often designed to be compact and practical, with slots for cards, cash, and other essentials.</li>



<li>Belts: Leather belts are typically handmade and can be customized with various buckles, colors, and textures.</li>



<li>Shoes and boots: Artisans skilled in shoemaking can produce high-quality leather footwear, ranging from casual shoes to formal dress shoes or sturdy boots.</li>



<li>Accessories: Leather can be transformed into accessories like bracelets, cuffs, keychains, and watch straps.</li>



<li>Leather garments: Some craftsmen specialize in creating leather jackets, vests, pants, or skirts.</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.25.58-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-190"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Resin</title>
		<link>https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/portfolio/resin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 19:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/?post_type=portfolio#038;p=182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol>
<li>Determine the Workshop Focus: Decide on the specific type of resin workshop you want to offer. It could be an introductory workshop for beginners, a workshop focused on a particular resin technique (e.g., resin pouring, resin casting, resin jewelry making), or an advanced workshop for experienced resin artists.</li>



<li>Plan the Workshop Content: Develop a curriculum or outline that covers the key concepts, techniques, and skills participants will learn during the workshop. Break it down into smaller modules, and consider providing step-by-step instructions, demonstrations, and examples.</li>



<li>Gather Materials and Tools: Identify the necessary materials and tools for the workshop, depending on the specific projects or techniques you&#8217;ll be teaching. This may include epoxy resin, silicone molds, mixing cups and sticks, pigments or dyes, protective gloves and aprons, heat guns or torches for removing bubbles, and a well-ventilated workspace</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://mohsamak.github.io/site1/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/WhatsApp-Image-2023-10-16-at-10.27.26-AM.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-183"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
